Guide to the Culver Family Papers, 1858-1915
Department of Special Collections
- Correspondence and Literary Drafts, 1859-1900s.
  - Oscar Culver, Fiction Drafts III, Undated., (5 documents, 23 pages) (Oversize 12, Folder 18)
  - Oscar Culver, Fiction Drafts, IV, Undated., (4 documents, 47 pages) (Oversize 12, Folder 19)
  - Oscar Culver Non-Fiction Drafts, Undated., (8 documents, 23 pages) (Oversize 12, Folder 20)
  - Oscar Culver Poetry Drafts, Dated & Undated., (12 documents, 35 pages) (Oversize 12, Folder 21)
  - Minnie B. Culver, Fiction & Poetry Drafts, Dated & Undated., (10 documents, 16 pages) (Oversize 12, Folder 22)
  - Julia Louise [Lulu] Culver, Fiction & Poetry Drafts, Dated & Undated [1900s?]., (7 documents, 18 pages) (Oversize 12, Folder 23)
    Galley proofs: The Wanderer & Other Poems.
  - Richard Keith Culver, Poetry Drafts, Dated & Undated., (2 pages, 5 x 7") (Oversize 12, Folder 24)
  - Literary Drafts, Attributed, Dated & Undated., (8 documents, 12 pages) (Oversize 12, Folder 25)
  - Literary Drafts, Unattributed, Dated & Undated., (14 documents, 13 pages) (Oversize 12, Folder 26)
- Correspondence & Misc. Papers, 1850s-1900s.
  - J. O. Culver, Legal Papers and Notes, 1850s-1900s., (16 documents) (Oversize 13, Folder 1)
  - J. O. Culver, Legal Papers and Notes, Undated., (7 documents) (Oversize 13, Folder 2)
  - J. Oscar Culver, Paymaster Notes, Dated & Undated., (5 documents) (Oversize 13, Folder 3)
    See also, Box 3, F23.
  - J. O. Culver, Postal Inspector Papers & Correspondence, 1882-1883., (24 documents) (Oversize 13, Folder 4)
  - J. O. Culver, Postal Inspector Papers & Correspondence, 1884-1886., (17 documents) (Oversize 13, Folder 5)
    See also Box 9, F16, Pocket Journal, 1886, for additional material J. O. Culver as Postal Inspector.
  - J. O. Culver, Postal Inspector Correspondence & Miscellaneous Papers, 1887-1902., (22 documents) (Oversize 13, Folder 6)
    See also Box 9, Folders 17, 19-21, and Box 10, F4, 6, for additional material on J. O. Culver as Postal Inspector.
  - J. O. Culver, Postal Inspector Correspondence & Miscellaneous Papers, Undated., (8 documents) (Oversize 13, Folder 7)
  - Julia Louise Culver School Papers, Dated & Undated., (10 documents) (Oversize 13, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Culver Family, Undated., (38 items) (Oversize 13, Folder 9)
  - Notes on "Greenleaf on Evidence.", (67 pages) (Oversize 13, Folder 10)
  - Organization Papers--Maxim Wagon Grease Co., 1910., (25 pages) (Oversize 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Neither to Nor from Culver Family [possibly Confederate], 1860-1863., (21 letters & 1 fragment). (Oversize 13, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Army Paymaster's Letterbook [and Index], Aug 1862-Nov 1865., (555 pages) (Oversize 14)
    Mainly copies of official correspondence to U.S. Army and government personnel (national and state) on payments due & disbursed, and other related matters. Index contains names of addressees and other individuals mentioned in the letters. [Some letters illegible owing to fading.] Transcribed copies of 120 of the letters also accompany the book.